<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alexandria Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Historical Places</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Shopping</string>

    <string name="roman_museum">Graeco Roman Museum</string>
    <string name="roman_desc">The Graeco-Roman Museum is an archaeological museum located
        in Alexandria, Egypt. Erected in 1892, it was first built in a five-room apartment,
        inside one small building on Rosetta Street (later Avenue Canope and now Horriya).
        In 1895, it was transferred to another, larger building near Gamal Abdul Nasser Street.
        The museum contains several pieces dating from the Graeco-Roman
        (Ptolemaic) era in the 3rd century BC, such as a sculpture of Apis in black granite,
        the sacred bull of the Egyptians, mummies, sarcophagus, tapestries, and other objects
        offering a view of Greco-Roman civilization in contact with ancient Egypt.\n\nThe museum\'s
        collection is the product of donations from wealthy Alexandrians as well as of excavations
        led by successive directors of the institution, both within the town and in its environs.
        Certain other objects have come from the Organization of Antiquities at Cairo
        (particularly those of the Pharaonic period) and from various digs undertaken
        at the beginning of the century in Fayoum and at Benhasa. Housed within a
        historic building whose beautiful neoclassical facade of six columns
        and pediment bears the large Greek inscription ‘MOYΣEION’ (MOUSEION).
        The museum consists of 27 halls and an attractive garden,
        which offer an excellent introduction to Egypt\'s Greco-Roman period.\n\nThe museum has been
        closed for renovations since 2005. As of June 2017,
        the building was still surrounded by scaffolding.</string>

    <string name="amphitheater">Ancient Roman Amphitheater</string>
    <string name="amphitheater_desc">Roman Amphitheatre or Roman Theatre is located in the central
        region of Alexandria city at Kom el-Dikka. Bordered by the Horrya Street in the north,
        Nabi Daniel Street in west, Abdel Moneim Street in south and Saphia Zaghloul
        Street from the eastern side, Roman Theatre is one of the symbols of Alexandria city.\n\n
        Basically Amphitheatre means double theatre and were grand and impressive in structure.
        Usually built in semi-circular shape, Amphitheatre was an open-airtheatre with no curtains on the stage.
        The Roman Theatre of Egypt is modest in size and most of the part of the structure
        is in ruined condition but still it is an excellent ancient structure of Roman period of Egypt.
        The theatre also consists of numerous galleries erected crudely.</string>

    <string name="heracleion">Sunken City of Heracleion</string>
    <string name="heracleion_desc">Heracleion (Ancient Greek: Ἡράκλειον), also known by its
        Egyptian name Thonis (Ancient Egyptian: Tȝ-ḥn.t, Coptic: ⲧϩⲱⲛⲓ, Ancient Greek: Θῶνις)
        and sometimes called Thonis-Heracleion, was an ancient Egyptian city located near
        the Canopic Mouth of the Nile, about 32 km northeast of Alexandria. Its ruins are located
        in Abu Qir Bay, currently 2.5 km off the coast, under 10 m (30 ft) of water.\n\n
        A stele found on the site indicates that it was one single city known by both its Egyptian and
        Greek names. Its legendary beginnings go back to as early as the 12th century BC, and it
        is mentioned by ancient Greek historians. Its importance grew particularly during the waning
        days of the Pharaohs.</string>

    <string name="san_stefano">San Stefano Mall and Hotel</string>
    <string name="san_stefano_desc">San Stefano (Arabic: سان إستفانو‎) is a neighborhood in
        Alexandria, Egypt. The area was known for a landmark hotel-casino that was demolished
        in the late 1990s. That hotel was replaced by the San Stefano Grand Plaza,
        a hotel-apartment-shopping mall complex that includes a Four Seasons luxury hotel,
        opened in 2007[1] and apartments, housed in the tallest building
        in Alexandria (135 m (443 ft))</string>

    <string name="city_center">Alexandria City Center</string>
    <string name="city_center_desc">Suitably located on the Alexandria Cairo Desert Road,
        opposite to the Alexandria International Park, City Centre Alexandria is just 15
        minutes from downtown.\n\n
        The landmark shopping destination opened in January 2003 to offer its customers a unique
        shopping and entertainment experience. The Centre has recently completed a massive
        extension programme that has increased the total number of retail stores in the
        mall from 97 to over 170, spread over a trading area of 60,370 square metres.\n\n
        With an eclectic mix of world class brands and retailers, a 14,771 square metre Carrefour
        Hypermarket, Vox Cinemas, an international food court and the popular family
        entertainment destination- Magic Planet- City Centre Alexandria is the biggest shopping mall
        in the city. It provides an international shopping experience to the residents and
        visitors of Alexandria.</string>

</resources>
